http://www.novastor.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

View Pricing
NovaStor offers all-inclusive pricing based on the volume of data you select to backup with unlimited servers and full application and hardware support.
Request a Quote
To request pricing based on your specific IT environment and backup volume requirements, request a quote.
Demo Setup
Try before you buy. Our backup experts are available to help you test our software in your environment through our complementary setup assistance.
Health Check
Wir überprüfen und optimieren Ihre Datensicherung nach IT-Umstellungen oder für Unternehmensprüfungen.
Individuelle Beratung
Unsere Backup-Experten beraten Sie mit Know-how und langjähriger Erfahrung und liefern individuelle Lösungen.
NovaStor Schulungen
In bewährten Schulungsformaten erwerben und erproben Sie die Fachkenntnisse für Ihren Backup- und Restore-Erfolg.
Whitepapers
NovaStor backup experts share their extensive experience and know-how through whitepapers.
Case Studies
View our case studies for references and to learn about some of our customer successes.
Technical Documents
Get detailed technical documentation for NovaStor products.
Videos
View our videos for step-by-step tutorials of NovaStor DataCenter software.
Webinars
Gain valuable knowledge, insight and technical guidance by viewing our webinars.
Certifications
Our certifications ensure that our products meet rigorous standards.
Company
We help overwhelmed and underfunded IT Admins alleviate their backup pains.
Careers
View available jobs and Careers at NovaStor.
News
Stay current on our news and press coverage.
Blog
Get valuable insight about data protection and more.
Contact
Get contact info, office hours or contact us.
Backup Solutions
Pricing
View Pricing
Request a Quote
Resources
Company
Careers
News
NovaStor CorporationLast updated: 12/21/2018
NovaStor is committed to protecting your privacy.
This Privacy Statement applies to data collected by NovaStor through its websites and product registration.
1. What This Privacy Policy Covers2. Control of Your Personal Information3. Types and Uses of Information We Collect4. Disclosure of Personal Information5. International Transfer of Information6. Changes in this Privacy Policy
1. What This Privacy Policy Covers
NovaStor takes the privacy and protection of personal information (“Personal Information”) very seriously. By visiting and using the Novastor websites, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.
This privacy policy describes NovaStor’s data collection, processing, and use of personal information and anonymous information collected when you visit or use any of our NovaStor owned websites or complete a product registration.
2. Control of Your Personal Information
Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information
You have the following data protection rights:
You can request access, correction, updates or deletions of your personal information.
You can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information.
If we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information.
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacy@novastor.com or by mail at NovaStor Corporation, 29209 Canwood Street, Agoura Hills, CA 91301 USA, Attention: Privacy. We will respond to your request to change, correct or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.
Controlling Unsolicited Email ("Spam")
NovaStor is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial email, or "spam." NovaStor will not sell, lease, or rent its email subscriber lists to third parties. NovaStor has taken precautions to ensure that unsolicited commercial marketing emails are not sent. We also require the inclusion of an opt-out mechanism and other required information to be included in every email sent through our marketing platform.
Unsubscribing from Our Communications
You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our emails, updating your communication preferences, or by send us an email at privacy@novastor.com or postal mail to NovaStor Corporation, 29209 Canwood Street, Agoura Hills, CA 91301 USA, Attention: Privacy. Customers cannot opt-out of receiving transactional emails related to their products or subscription service with us.
3. Types and Use of Information We Collect
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
In general, information you submit to us is used by us to respond to requests that you make, to better tailor our messaging and support, and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and learning. We also use this information to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf. We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information that makes the information personally identifiable to you.
Here are the types of information we collect:
"Personal Information"
Personal information is information that is personally identifiable like names, addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.
We collect the following Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily:
Upon accessing our websites, certain usage information is automatically collected and then saved. This information that can directly or indirectly identify an individual includes, among other things, your Internet Protocol (IP) address and geographical location.
If you fill out any of the forms on our websites, we collect any Personal Information you may provide, including but not limited to, your name, company, country, email address, phone number the details of your request or any other information you choose to provide.
When you contact us by email, chat or phone, we may collect Personal Information you provide us voluntarily in connection with this communication.
Personal Information can also include transactions that you enter on the website, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.
If you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing for all online orders. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf. For direct purchases, as in the case with larger business accounts, we will ask for purchasing information directly, such as your credit card number and billing address, which will be used to create a NovaStor billing account. Except for this, we do not collect Sensitive Information from you.
“Automatic Data Collection and Anonymous Information”
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. This automatic exchange of data between your browser and our server upon accessing our pages informs us of data like which browser you are using, your referral source, date and length of visit and pages viewed.
The information we collect automatically is called “Anonymous Information.” Anonymous Information means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Thus, Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons.
We may use this Anonymous Information for internal purposes, such as maintaining our operating ability, preventing fraudulent access to our websites or analyzing usage patterns so that we may enhance our websites. We also reserve the right to use and disclose any Anonymous Information at our discretion, although you will remain anonymous as an individual user.
We automatically collect information through different technologies as described below.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Our website uses technologies such as Cookies, web beacons, tags and scripts. These technologies are used to analyze trends, administer the websites, track users’ movements around the websites and to gather demographic information about our user-base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by their respective providers on an aggregated basis.
Use of Cookies
NovaStor websites use "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content on your later visits to these sites.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. In addition, you can delete Cookies that have already been saved on your computer at any time.
Use of Web Beacons
NovaStor websites may contain electronic images known as web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional email messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. NovaStor may also employ web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of our sites. We prohibit web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.
When you receive newsletters or promotional email from NovaStor, we may use web beacons, customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the email has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused email communications or other information.
Google Analytics
Our website may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google uses Cookies to help analyze the use of our websites. On behalf of NovaStor, Google Analytics uses cookies to examine your interaction with NovaStor websites.
Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the Site, compile reports on Site activity and provide other Site activity and internet related services. In addition, Google may also transfer this information to third parties if required by law or if third parties process the information on Google’s behalf.
We use Google Analytics on our blog to track social shares made from our website. Google automatically collect and store certain information in their server logs which includes device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL, cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Google Account, in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy
By using NovaStor websites, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described and for the aforementioned purpose. More information about Google Analytics can be found here.
Advertising and Partnerships
We partner with a third-party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, and you are located in the European Union, go here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.
From time to time, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party sources including partners with which we offer co-branded services or engage in joint marketing activities, and publicly available sources such as social media websites.
We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your Personal Information to the third party.
Social Sharing
We embed a Facebook widget on our blog to allow you to see number of likes/shares/recommends and “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update
We use a Twitter Tweet widget on our blog. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update
We use a GooglePlus widget on our blog. As a result, our website makes requests to Google’s servers for you to be able to share our webpages using your GooglePlus account. These requests make your IP address visible to Google, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy
We use a Linkedin Share widget on our blog to allow you to share our webpages on Linkedin. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
We use Pinterest Save widget on our blog to allow you to pin images to Pinterest from our webpages. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy
We use Reddit Badge widget at our website which may log information when you interact with the widget. This may include your IP address, user-agent string, browser type, operating system, referral URLs, device information (e.g., device IDs), pages visited, links clicked, user interactions (e.g., voting data), the requested URL and hardware settings, in accordance with their privacy policy: https://www.redditinc.com/policies/privacy-policy
Security of Your Personal Information
NovaStor is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. Also, we recommend that you do not save your password in a so-called password manager.
Privacy of Minors
Our websites are not intended for or targeted at children under 16, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 16. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 16, please contact us at privacy@novastor.com, so that we may delete the information.
4. Disclosure of Personal Information
Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of NovaStor and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.
We reserve the right to provide your personal information to NovaStor distribution partners solely in order to allow them to offer advice and/or sell NovaStor products and services. Our distribution partners are prohibited from using your personal information unless the use is directly related to NovaStor.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of NovaStor or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of NovaStor employees, customers or the public.
5. International Transfer of Information
Personal information collected on NovaStor sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which NovaStor or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. By using our web site or a NovaStor service, you agree that your personal information may be transferred to any country in which NovaStor or its affiliates, subsidiaries or distribution partners maintain facilities.
6. Changes in this Privacy Policy
We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services or based on customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. If there are material changes to this statement or in how NovaStor will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how NovaStor is protecting your information.
Enforcement of This Privacy Statement
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us.
Contacting Us
NovaStor welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us.
For further Information on NovaStor offices, please go to our contact page.
Company, Inc
Street AddressCity, ST 00000Call us: 1-800-COMPANY(800-000-0000)
NovaStor Corporation29209 Canwood St.Agoura Hills, CA 91301 USA
Tel.: +1 805-579-6700Fax.: +1 805-579-6710info@novastor.com
GERMAN OFFICE
NovaStor GmbHNeumann-Reichardt-Straße 27-3322041 Hamburg
Tel.: +49 40 63809 0Fax.: +49 40 63809 62kontakt@novastor.de
Newsletter signup:
© 2020 NovaStor. All Rights Reserved.
About UsSupportProductsPricingPartnershipsBlog
© 2020 NovaStor. All Rights Reserved.Terms | Privacy | Sitemap
Switch to German website
NovaStor Corporation29209 Canwood St.Agoura Hills, CA 91301 USA
Tel.: +1 805-579-6700Fax.: +1 805-579-6710info@novastor.com
Newsletter signup:
